# VLAD VIRLAN

Software Engineer

#### CONTACT

- +44 7578 222707
- ✓ vladvirlan.dev@gmail.com
- 27 Dalston Gardens, London
- wladvirlan.github.io

# **EDUCATION**

# University

2024 - PresentB.Sc. in Computer Science atQueen Mary, University of London

# AWARDS & CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Full-Stack Developer
- Certified Python Al Developer
- Certified TypeScript Developer
- Certified Swift Developer

# SKILLS

- Knowledge of systems and Architecture
- Communication and collaboration skills
- Software development skills
- Problem-solving skills
- Organisation and time management skills

#### **PROFILE**

I am a Computer Science undergraduate at a Russell Group University with a passion for software engineering. With expertise in Python and Java, I am ardent about problemsolving and often use my knowledge of mathematics and physics to tackle all manners of challenges that come my way. I bring resilience, discipline and hard work to every team I collaborate with and I am excited to contribute to the ever expanding industry that is the field of technology.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

TEACHING ASSISTANT

# Park High School and Sixth Form

June 2024 - July 2024

- Shadowed a Teaching Assistant and studied support strategies
- Helped students debug code
- Assisted with coding projects and reinforcing key programming principles
- Supported students with mathematical concepts and created personalised learning materials
- Created a Python learning resource

# TUTOR

# Self-Employed

September 2022 - Present

- Taught GCSE Maths and Computer Science
- Taught BTEC Level 3 Computing
- I continue to support individuals in Maths and Computer Science, offering guidance on their specific needs